Guide to the Rand School of Social Science Records TAM.007
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: General Correspondence, 1913-1957
  - General Correspondence, Jul 1941 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - General Correspondence, Aug 1941 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, Sep 1941 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, Oct 1941 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, Nov 1941 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, Dec 1941 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, 1941 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, Jan 1942 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, Feb 1942 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, Mar 1942 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, Apr 1942 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, May 1942 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence, Jun 1942 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence, Jul 1942 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence, Aug 1942 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence, Sep 1942 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence, Oct 1942 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence, Nov 1942 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - General Correspondence, Dec 1942 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - General Correspondence, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - General Correspondence, Jan 1943-Jun 1943 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - General Correspondence, Jul 1943-Dec 1943 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - General Correspondence, 1943 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - General Correspondence, Jan 1944 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, Feb 1944 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, Mar 1944 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, Apr 1944 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, May 1944 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, Jun 1, 1944-Jun 15, 1944 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    Film R-7124, Reel 36: Frame XIII:B
  - General Correspondence, Jun 16, 1944-Jun 30, 1944 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, Jul 1944 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, Aug 1944 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, Sep 1944 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, Oct 1944 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence, Nov 1944 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence, Dec 1944 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence, Jan 1945 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence, Feb 1945 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence, Mar 1945 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence, Apr 1945 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - General Correspondence, May 1945 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, Jun 1, 1945-Jun 15, 1945 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, Jun 16, 1945-Jun 30, 1945 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, Jul 1945 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, Aug 1945 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, Sep 1945 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, Oct 1945 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, Nov 1945 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, Dec 1945 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, 1945 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, Jan 1946 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, Feb 1946 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    Film R-7124, Reel 37: Frame XIII:B
  - General Correspondence, Mar 1946 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, Apr 1946 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, May 1946 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, Jun 1946 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, Jul 1946 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, Aug 1946 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, Sep 1946 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, Oct 1946 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, Nov 1946 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence, Dec 1946 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence, 1946 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence, Jan 1947 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence, Feb 1947 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence, Mar 1947 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, Apr 1947 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, May 1947 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, Jun 1947 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, Jul 1947 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, Aug 1947 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, Sep 1947 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, Oct 1947 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, Nov 1947 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, Dec 1947 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence, Jan 1948 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence, Feb 1948 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    Film R-7124, Reel 38: Frame XIII:B
  - General Correspondence, Mar 1948 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence, Apr 1948 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence, May 1948 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, Jun 1948 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, Jul 1948 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, Aug 1948 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, Sep 1948 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, Oct 1948 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, Nov 1948 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, Dec 1, 1948-Dec 8, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, Dec 9, 1948-Dec 29, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, Jan 1949 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence, Feb 1949 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence, Mar 1949 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence, Apr 1949 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, May 1, 1949 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, Jun 1949 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, Jul 1949 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, Aug 1949 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, Sep 1949 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, Oct 1949 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, Nov 1949 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, Dec 1949 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, 1949 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, Jan 1950-Mar 1950 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, Apr 1950-Jun 1950 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Film R-7124, Reel 39: Frame XIII:B
  - General Correspondence, Jul 1950-Sep 1950 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, Oct 1950-Dec 1950 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, Jan 1951-Mar 1951 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, Apr 1951-Jun 1951 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, Jul 1951-Dec 1951 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, 1951 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, Jan 1952-Mar 1952 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, Apr 1952-Jun 1952 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence, Jul 1952-Sep 1952 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence, Oct 1952-Dec 1952 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence, Jan 1953-Mar 1953 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence, Apr 1953-Jun 1953 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence, Jul 1953-Sep 1953 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, Oct 1953-Dec 1953 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, Jan 1954-Mar 1954 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, Apr 1954-Jun 1954 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, Jul 1954-Sep 1954 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, Oct 1954-Nov 1954 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, Dec 1954 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, Jan 1, 1955-Jan 10, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, Jan 11, 1955-Jan 20, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence, Jan 21, 1955-Jan 31, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence, Feb 1955 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence, Mar 1955 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence, Apr 1955 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence, May 1955 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence, Jun 1955 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - General Correspondence, Jul 1955 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - General Correspondence, Aug 1955 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - General Correspondence, Sep 1955 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - General Correspondence, Oct 1955 (Box 24, Folder 21, Box 25, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, Nov 1955-Dec 1955 (Box 24, Folder 22, Box 25, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    Film R-7124, Reel 40: Frame XIII:B
  - General Correspondence, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence: pt 1, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence: pt 2, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Series III: Course Records, 1917-1955
  - Subseries IIIA: Course Records and Correspondence, 1925-1953
    Course Records and Correspondence consists of 82 subject files which pertain to courses, lectures, forums, and special educational programs sponsored by the Rand School. The subject files are arranged in alphabetical order according to the title of the file. Within most of these files are course records (course outlines, syllabi, class exercises, examinations, related papers) and correspondence relating to a particular course. For each file in which those types of materials are found, the course records precede the correspondence in the filming order. All correspondence in these files is chronologically arranged and pertains to such matters as obtaining faculty members and scheduling courses in the School's curriculum for a particular semester. Among the more interesting items in this part are the papers relating to correspondence courses (XIII:C:9), teacher in service courses (XIII:C:18 XIII:C:19), juvenile delinquency courses (XIII:C:23XIII:C:24), the Newark School of Social Science (XIII:C:31), peace education (XIII:C:34), propaganda courses (XIII:C:38 XIII:C:39), the Rand High School (XIII:C:45), the Rand School in Northern New Jersey (XIII:C:46), teacher coaching courses (XIII:C:58 XIII:C:65), the Trade Union Institute (XIII:C:66 XIII:C:69), women's afternoon classes (XIII:C:74 XIII:C:76), and the Workers' Training Course (XIII:C:77XIII:C:78).
    - Course Announcements and Outlines, 1925-Fall 1931, undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
      Film R-7124, Reel 40: Frame XIII:C:1
    - Course Announcements and Outlines, Winter 1932-Winter 1933, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Course Announcements and Outlines, Fall 1933 -Winter 1935, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Course Announcements and Outlines, Fall 1935 -Winter 1937 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Course Announcements and Outlines, Fall 1937 -Winter 1939 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Course Announcements and Outlines, Fall 1937-Winter 1939 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Course Announcements and Outlines, Fall 1938 -Winter 1939 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Course Announcements and Outlines, Fall 1939 -Winter 1940 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Course Announcements and Outlines, Fall 1940 -Winter 1941 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Course Announcements and Outlines, Fall 1941 -Winter 1943 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Course Announcements and Outlines, Winter 1944 -Winter 1953 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Course Announcements and Outlines, undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Alertness Credit for Teachers, Course Records and Correspondence, Aug 17, 1933-Feb 12, 1938 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      Film R-7124, Reel 40: Frame XIII:C:2
    - The American Theater: Its Present and Future, Lecture Records and Correspondence, Mar 12, 1931-Sep 12, 1931 (Box 26, Folder 8)
      Film R-7124, Reel 40: Frame XIII:C:3
    - Brooklyn Forum, Records and Correspondence, Oct 25, 1944-May 12, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 9)
      Film R-7124, Reel 40: Frame XIII:C:4
    - Building Service Employees Union, Local 32B, Course Records and Correspondence, Feb 9, 1936-Jun 9, 1937 (Box 26, Folder 10)
      Film R-7124, Reel 40: Frame XIII:C:5
    - Child Institute, Records and Correspondence, Jan 6, 1929- May 10, 1930 (Box 26, Folder 11)
      Film R-7124, Reel 40: Frame XIII:C:6
    - Children with Mental Retarded Development, Course Records, Apr 1940 (Box 26, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 40: Frame XIII:C:7
    - "Communism vs. The Schools", Apr 8, 1941-May 15, 1941 (Box 26, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 40: Frame XIII:C:8
    - Correspondence Courses, Course Records and Corres­pondence, Nov 29, 1932-Apr 23, 1934 (Box 26, Folder 14)
      Film R-7124, Reel 40: Frame XIII:C:9
    - Current Trade Union Policies, Course Records and Correspondence, Jul 30, 1942-Oct 26, 1942,, undated (Box 26, Folder 15)
      Film R-7124, Reel 40: Frame XIII:C:10
    - Debs School of Social Science, Lecture Series, 1936-01, Feb 1936 (Box 26, Folder 16)
      Film R-7124, Reel 40: Frame XIII:C:11
    - Education for Democracy, Course Records and Corres­pondence, Jan 10, 1939-Oct 4, 1939 (Box 26, Folder 17)
      Film R-7124, Reel 40: Frame XIII:C:12
    - Employment Interviewer Counselor, Course Records and Correspondence, May 16, 1938-Jul 22, 1938 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 40: Frame XIII:C:13
    - Employment Interviewer Counselor, Course Records and Correspondence, May 16, 1938-Jul 22, 1938 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Forums, 1929, 1936, undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 40: Frame XIII:C:14
    - The Rapture of American Labor, Lecture Records and Correspondence, Jul 24, 1931-Feb 8, 1932 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      Film R-7124, Reel 40: Frame XIII:C:15
    - Home Economics, Course Records and Correspondence, Mar 1940 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      Film R-7124, Reel 40: Frame XIII:C:16
    - How Trade Unions Work, Course Records and Corres­pondence, Aug 10, 1942-Oct 15, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      Film R-7124, Reel 40: Frame XIII:C:17
    - In-Service Courses, Course Records and Correspondence, Jun 2, 1938-Jan 14, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      Film R-7124, Reel 40: Frame XIII:C:18
    - In-Service Course: New Tendencies and Techniques in Guidance, Course Materials, 1937-1938 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      Film R-7124, Reel 40: Frame XIII:C:19
    - Institute for Russian Studies, Records and Correspondence, Feb 7, 1944-Apr 5, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 9)
      Film R-7124, Reel 40: Frame XIII:C:20
    - "Is Socialism Still Valid?", Conference Records and Correspondence, Jan 5, 1943-Jan 20, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 10)
      Film R-7124, Reel 40: Frame XIII:C:21
    - Issues and Aims in the Labor Movement, Course Records & Correspondence Records and Correspondence, Aug 17, 1941-Nov 1941 (Box 27, Folder 11)
      Film R-7124, Reel 41: Frame XIII:C:22
    - Juvenile Delinquency Symposium, Course Records and Correspondence Correspondence, May 18, 1937-Jul 1937 (Box 27, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 41: Frame XIII:C:23
    - Juvenile Delinquency Symposium, Course Records and Correspondence Correspondence, Aug 1937-Mar 4, 1938 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Juvenile Delinquency, Course Outlines & Records, Winter 1938 -Winter 1939 (Box 27, Folder 14)
      Film R-7124, Reel 41: Frame XIII:C:24
    - Juvenile Delinquency Correspondence, Dec 24, 1937-Aug 30, 1938 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Juvenile Delinquency Correspondence, Sep 1, 1938-May 2, 1939 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - "Labor and Social Democracy, Here and Abroad", Conference Records and Correspondence, May 22, 1945-Jul 10, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 41: Frame XIII:C:25
    - "Labor and the Next Congress", Conference Records and Correspondence and Correspondence and Correspondence and Correspondence, Aug 18, 1942-Oct 17, 1942 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 41: Frame XIII:C:26
    - Luncheon Discussion Speakers, Records and Correspondence, Aug 17, 1931-May 8, 1934, undated (Box 28, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 41: Frame XIII:C:27
    - Millinery Workers Union, Local 24, Course Records and Correspondence, Jan 25, 1936, Jan 22, 1938 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      Film R-7124, Reel 41: Frame XIII:C:28
    - Nation, Race, and Class, Course Records and Correspondence, May 11, 1933-Aug 24, 1933 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      Film R-7124, Reel 41: Frame XIII:C:29
    - Newark Forum, Records and Correspondence, Dec 18, 1945-Mar 1, 1947, undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
      Film R-7124, Reel 41: Frame XIII:C:30
    - Newark School of Social Science, Course Records and Correspondence, Oct 7, 1937-Jan 1940, undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
      Film R-7124, Reel 41: Frame XIII:C:31
    - New Directions in Socialist Thought, Course Records and Correspondence and Correspondence and Correspondence, Jun 19, 1941-Dec 1, 1941, 1941 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      Film R-7124, Reel 41: Frame XIII:C:32
    - Organization Work for Socialist Party Members, Course Records and Correspondence, Oct 4, 1934, Sep 23, 1935 (Box 28, Folder 9)
      Film R-7124, Reel 41: Frame XIII:C:33
    - Peace Education: Materials and Methods, Course Records and Correspondence, Mar 26, 1936-Dec 28, 1938 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      Film R-7124, Reel 41: Frame XIII:C:34
    - Peace Education: Materials and Methods, Course Records and Correspondence, Mar 26, 1936-Dec 28, 1938 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Peace Education: Materials and Methods, Course Records and Correspondence, Mar 26, 1936-Dec 28, 1938 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Peace Education: Materials and Methods, Course Records and Correspondence, Jan 5, 1938-Dec 28, 1938 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Philadelphia Forum, Records and Correspondence, Fall 1938, Oct 7, 1946-Dec 24, 1946 (Box 28, Folder 14)
      Film R-7124, Reel 41: Frame XIII:C:35
    - Points of Conflict in Modern Education, Course Records, Feb 1939-May 1939 (Box 28, Folder 15)
      Film R-7124, Reel 41: Frame XIII:C:36
    - Points of Conflict in Modern Education, Course Records, Feb 1939-May 1939 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Points of Conflict in Modern Education, Course Records, Feb 1939-May 1939 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - A Program for America: Forum Records and Correspondence, Oct 23, 1935-Jan 30, 1936 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 41: Frame XIII:C:37
    - Propaganda & Public Opinion: Course Records, Correspondence, Feb 23, 1938-Dec 16, 1938 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 41: Frame XIII:C:38
    - Propaganda Analysis & Public Opinion: Course Records, Correspondence, Jun 17, 1939-Sep 29, 1939 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 41: Frame XIII:C:39
    - "Prophets of Our Time" (First Series), Correspondence Re: Publication, Apr 5, 1944-May 25, 1945 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      Film R-7124, Reel 41: Frame XIII:C:40
    - "Prophets of Our Time" (Second Series), Lecture Records and Correspondence, Oct 25, 1944-Apr 13, 1945 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      Film R-7124, Reel 41: Frame XIII:C:41
    - Psychological Contributions to American Life: Correspondence, Oct 1, 1932-Mar 22, 1934 (Box 29, Folder 6)
      Film R-7124, Reel 41: Frame XIII:C:42
    - Public Speaking, Course Correspondence, Apr 24, 1944-Apr 5, 1945, undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
      Film R-7124, Reel 41: Frame XIII:C:43
    - Race Theories and Democracy, Course Records and Correspondence, May 29, 1939, Oct 16, 1939 (Box 29, Folder 8)
      Film R-7124, Reel 41: Frame XIII:C:44
    - Rand High School, 1935-1936 (Box 29, Folder 9)
      Film R-7124, Reel 41: Frame XIII:C:45
    - Rand School in Northern New Jersey, Apr 7, 1947, Dec 1949, undated (Box 29, Folder 10)
      Film R-7124, Reel 42: Frame XIII:C:46
    - Rand School in Northern New Jersey, Apr 7, 1947, Dec 1949, undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Rand School Summer Institute, 1930 (Box 29, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 42: Frame XIII:C:47
    - "Russia and the Post-War World", Conference Records and Correspondence, Apr 1, 1943-Apr 19, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 42: Frame XIII:C:48
    - Russia Under the Czars and Soviets, Course Records and Correspondence, Sep 1, 1944-Mar 12, 1945 (Box 29, Folder 14)
      Film R-7124, Reel 42: Frame XIII:C:49
    - SDF-ALP Forum, Records and Correspondence, Dec 31, 1942-Jan 4, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 42: Frame XIII:C:50
    - Social and Economic Planning, Course Records and Correspondence, Jul 10, 1931-Oct 21, 1931 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 42: Frame XIII:C:51
    - Social Case Work, Course Records and Correspondence, Nov 6, 1937-Sep 13, 1938 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 42: Frame XIII:C:52
    - Social Forces in Modern Education: Course Records and Correspondence, Dec 14, 1937-Jun 22, 1938 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      Film R-7124, Reel 42: Frame XIII:C:53
    - Social Investigator, Course Records and Correspondence, Jan 5, 1938-Jan 18, 1939 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      Film R-7124, Reel 42: Frame XIII:C:54
    - Social Security Symposium, Course Records and Correspondence, Jun 1, 1938, Oct 26, 1938 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      Film R-7124, Reel 42: Frame XIII:C:55
    - Social Welfare Problems, Course Records and Corres­pondence, Apr 23, 1938-Jan 11, 1939 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      Film R-7124, Reel 42: Frame XIII:C:56
    - Supervision, Course Records and Correspondence, Apr 22, 1938-Jan 1939 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      Film R-7124, Reel 42: Frame XIII:C:57
    - Teacher Coaching Courses, Course Records and Correspondence, Jul 16, 1938-Jan 24, 1941, undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
      Film R-7124, Reel 42: Frame XIII:C:58
    - Teacher Coaching Courses, Course Records and Correspondence, Jul 16, 1938-Jan 24, 1941, undated (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Teacher Coaching Course: Children with Mental Retarded Development & Low I.Q.: Course Records and Correspondence, Sep 1938 (Box 30, Folder 11)
      Film R-7124, Reel 42: Frame XIII:C:59
    - Teacher Coaching Course: Economics and Economic Geography, Course Records & Correspondence, Sep 1938 (Box 30, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 42: Frame XIII:C:60
    - Teacher Coaching Course: English Department Supervisor, Course Materials, Sep 1940 (Box 30, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 42: Frame XIII:C:61
    - Teacher Coaching Course: English for Junior and Senior High School, Course Records and Correspondence, Sep 22, 1938-Oct 10, 1938 (Box 30, Folder 14)
      Film R-7124, Reel 42: Frame XIII:C:62
    - Teacher Coaching Course: Junior School Clerk, Course Materials, undated (Box 30, Folder 15)
      Film R-7124, Reel 42: Frame XIII:C:63
    - Teacher Coaching Course: Kindergarten, Course Materials, 1940 (Box 30, Folder 16)
      Film R-7124, Reel 42: Frame XIII:C:64
    - Teacher Coaching Course: Speech Improvement, Course Materials, 1938 (Box 30, Folder 17)
      Film R-7124, Reel 42: Frame XIII:C:65
    - Trade Union Institute, Course Announcements and Outlines, 1936-1953, undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
      : Frame XIII:C:66
    - Trade Union Institute, Correspondence, Jan 24, 1936-Dec 1938, undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 43: Frame XIII:C:67
    - Trade Union Institute, Correspondence, Mar 5, 1936-Nov 2, 1945, undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Trade Union Institute, Correspondence, Mar 5, 1936-Nov 2, 1945, undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Trade Union Training Course, Newark, Nov 2, 1945-Oct 16, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      Film R-7124, Reel 43: Frame XIII:C:68
    - Trade Union Training Course, Philadelphia, Records and Correspondence, Oct 18, 1944-Oct 29, 1945 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      Film R-7124, Reel 43: Frame XIII:C:69
    - Wage and Hour Inspector, Course Records and Corres­pondence, Jan 26, 1939, 1939 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      Film R-7124, Reel 43: Frame XIII:C:70
    - "War Aims, Peace Terms, and the World After the War", Correspondence, Apr 21, 1941, 1942, undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
      Film R-7124, Reel 43: Frame XIII:C:71
    - War and Peace Education, Course Records and Correspondence, Jun 27, 1938-Oct 21, 1938 (Box 31, Folder 9)
      Film R-7124, Reel 43: Frame XIII:C:72